<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chofu_Dorm</string>


    <string name="list_how_unit">Unit</string>
    <string name="list_how_lounge">Lounge</string>
    <string name="list_how_Kitchen">Kitchen</string>
    <string name="list_how_smoking">Smoking</string>
    <string name="list_how_garbage">Garbage</string>
    <string name="list_how_laundry">Laundry</string>

    <string name="Lounge_caution">
        ☑Feel free to use these lounge rooms!\n☑Be careful not to be too noisy at night.\n☑Please keep your valuables with you.
    </string>
    <string name="Lounge_secondLounge">
        ☑This is in another building and able to be used until 10pm.\n However you need make a reservation ahead of time
    </string>

    <string name="Kitchen_caution1">
        ☑Wash and dry the tableware and utensils after each use.\n☑Return them to their original locations before you leave the kitchen.
    </string>

    <string name="Kitchen_refrigerator">
        ☑Food must be stored in the refrigerator in each individual’s room\n
        ☑All items stored in the communal refrigerator must be clearly marked with date and room number.\n
        ☑Your food might be abandoned if you leave it for a while if it doesn’t have personal information on it.\n
        ☑Basically, you should pick your food up before one week pass
    </string>
    <string name="Kitchen_rice">
        ☑Do not leave cooked rice in the rice cooker.\n☑Wash the container and inner lid.

    </string>

    <string name="Kitchen_towel">
        ☑Please use white towels to clean dishes and blue ones for tables.
    </string>

    <string name="Kitchen_Individual">
        ☑Seasoning and food for personal use must be kept in your own food box.
    </string>

    <string name="Unit_caution">
        ☑Cleaners come a few times a week. \n
        ☑Do not cook here except boiling water.\n
        ☑Overnight staying of non-residents from midnight to 8 o’clock in the morning is strictly prohibited.\n
        ☑The wall is so thin that the sound you make in your room can go through to others’ rooms and vise versa. Let’s not be too noisy.\n
    </string>
    <string name="Unit_shower">
        ☑Clear away your hair and dry the floor of the shower room after each use.
    </string>
    


</resources>
